Local 1199 Drug Division Records 5206-D
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Old boxes 53-55 (Box 53)
  - Appeals-Classification, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Attorneys-Correspondence, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Bill of Rights-Committee for Defense, 1951-1952 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Brotherhood Fund, 1962-1963 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - CIO Council-Nassau-Suffolk, 1956-1957 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Civil Rights-Cases, 1947-1956 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Civil Rights-Housing, 1961-1963 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Civil Service, 1952-1967 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Civil Service, 1952-1967 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Civil Service, 1952-1967 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Civil Service, 1952-1967 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Civil Service, 1952-1967 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Civil Service, 1952-1967 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Civil Service, 1963-1967 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Civil Service, 1963-1967 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Civil Service, 1963-1967 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Civil Service, 1963-1967 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Civil Service, 1963-1967 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Civil Service, 1963-1967 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Commission on Inflation & Economic Welfare, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 32)
- Old boxes 56-58 (Box 56)
  - Delegates Banquet, 1966-1968 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Delegates Banquet, 1966-1968 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Distributive, Processing & Officer Workers, 1947-1955 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Distributive, Processing & Officer Workers, 1947-1955 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Distributive Workers Union, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Drew, R. L., 1957-1960 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Drug Costs, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Drug News, 1951-1952 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Education, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Elections, 1958-1968 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Elections, 1958-1968 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Elections, 1958-1968 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Elections, 1958-1968 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Elections, 1958-1968 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Elections, 1958-1968 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Elections, 1958-1968 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Elections, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Elections, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Elections for Steward, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Fair Trade, 1951-1956 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Fair Trade, 1951-1956 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Form Letters, 1958-1962 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Old boxes 59-61 (Box 59)
  - Harlem, 1948-1949 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Health Care, 1960-1972 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Health Care, 1960-1972 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Health Care, 1960-1972 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Health Care, 1960-1972 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Health Emergency, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Health Facilities, 1965-1969 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Health Facilities, 1965-1969 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Health Facilities, 1965-1969 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Health Insurance-Financing, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Health Insurance-Financing, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Health Insurance-Financing, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Health Insurance Plan (HIP), 1958-1972 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Health Insurance Plan (HIP), 1958-1972 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Health Research Council, 1968-1971 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Health Systems Statistics, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Hiring Hall Data, 1956-1963 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Housing Project, Neighborhood, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Independent Stores-Organization, 1965-1967 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Insurance, 1950-1952 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - International Labor Press Association, 1956-1964 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Leaflets, 1956-1964 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Leaflets, 1956-1964 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Leaflets, 1956-1964 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Old boxes 62-64 (Box 62)
  - Legislation-Civil Liberties, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Legislation-Community Service Society, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Legislation-Health Maintenance Organizations (HMO) "Legislative Memo", 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Legislation-Manpower, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Legislation-Miscellaneous, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Legislation-Montoya & Long (Senator's), 1966-1968 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Legislation-N.Y.S. Health Insurance, 1970-1971 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Legislation-N.Y.S. Issues, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Legislation-N.Y.S. Manpower Training & Distribution, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Legislation-N.Y.S. Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Legislation-N.Y.S. Prevention and Early Detection, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Legislation-N.Y.S., 1945-1954 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Legislation-N.Y.S., 1945-1954 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Legislation-Peace Referendum Committee, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Legislation-Pension, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Legislation-Smith Act, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Legislative-Letters of Protest, Support, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Committee, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - March of Labor, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Meeting Notices, 1948-1954 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Mimeo's-Union Letters, 1948-1949 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Minimum Wage, 1954-1967 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Minority Groups-Employment, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Mobilization for Youth, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Municipal Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Old boxes 65-67 (Box 65)
  - N.Y.C. CIO Council, 1953-1956 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - N.Y.C. Department of Labor, 1959-1965 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - N.Y.C. Central Labor Council, 1957-1963 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - N.Y.S. AFL-CIO Council, 1957-1963 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - N.Y.S. Board of Mediation, 1959-1966 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - N.Y.S. Board of Mediation, 1959-1966 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - N.Y.S. Board of Mediation-NLRB, 1940-1952 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - N.Y.S. CIO Council, 1953-1957 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - N.Y.S. Department of Labor, 1950-1963 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - N.Y.S. Department of Labor-B.N.A., 1957-1961 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - N.Y.S. Department of Labor-State Mediation, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Other Unions, 1961-1969 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Officers, Installation of, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Opposition to Union, 1936 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - PAC, 1951-1961 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - PAC, 1951-1961 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Peace Referendum, 1952 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Pharmacists, Union of Greater N.Y., 1936 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Pharmaceutical Law, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Pharmaceutical Law, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Pharmaceutical Law, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Pharmacy Education Trust Fund, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Political Action Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Pre-Paid Prescription Plans, 1966-1968 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Pre-Paid Prescription Plans, 1966-1968 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Pre-Paid Prescription Plans, 1966-1968 (Box 65, Folder 26)
- Old boxes 68-70 (Box 68)
  - Pre-Paid Prescription Plans, 1967-1968 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Pre-Paid Prescription Plans, 1967-1968 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Professionalism and Unionism, 1955-1972 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Resolutions, 1946 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Retail Employees of America, United, 1937 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers, (RWDSU), 1939-1964 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers, (RWDSU), 1939-1964 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers, (RWDSU), 1939-1964 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers, (RWDSU), 1939-1964 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers, (RWDSU), 1939-1964 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers, (RWDSU), 1939-1964 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers, (RWDSU), 1939-1964 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers, (RWDSU), 1939-1964 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Social Security Amendments (HR 1), 1971-1972 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Social Security Amendments (HR 1), 1971-1972 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Sodamen, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Stores Under Organization, Leaflets, 1955-1963 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Strike Leaflets, 1948-1952 (Box 68, Folder 21)
- Tauber, Joseph L., 1958-1963 (Box 71-72, Folder 1)
- Tischenkel-Kennedy Airport, 1957-1960 (Box 71-72, Folder 2)
- Training, 1963-1967 (Box 71-72, Folder 3)
- Training and Upgrading Fund, 1969-1971 (Box 71-72, Folder 4)
- Training and Upgrading Fund, 1969-1971 (Box 71-72, Folder 5)
- Training and Upgrading Fund, 1969-1971 (Box 71-72, Folder 6)
- Training-Drug Clerks & Cosmeticians, 1964-1968 (Box 71-72, Folder 7)
- Training-Drug Clerks & Cosmeticians, 1964-1968 (Box 71-72, Folder 8)
- Training-Drug Clerks & Cosmeticians, 1964-1968 (Box 71-72, Folder 9)
- Training-Drug Clerks & Cosmeticians, 1964-1968 (Box 71-72, Folder 10)
- Training-Drug Clerks & Cosmeticians, 1964-1968 (Box 71-72, Folder 11)
- Training-Drug Clerks & Cosmeticians, 1964-1968 (Box 71-72, Folder 12)
- Training-Drug Delegates, 1969 (Box 71-72, Folder 13)
- Twenty-fifth Anniversary, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Twenty-fifth Anniversary, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Twenty-fifth Anniversary, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Unemployment Insurance, 1948-1956 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Union Democracy Built, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Unions, Misc., 1950 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- United Labor Action Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Wage Stabilization Board, 1951-1952 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Wage Stabilization Board, 1951-1952 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Wage Stabilization Board, 1951-1952 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Wage Stabilization Board, 1951-1952 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Wage Survey, Independent Stores, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- War Labor Board, 1945 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Affairs-All Division and General, 1950-1966 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Affairs Committee-Kiddie Party, 1952-1959 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Affairs Committee Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Affairs Reports, 1953-1958 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Affairs Sports and hobbies, 1940-1955 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Affairs-Teen Time, 1954-1959 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Benefit Plan-Spanish & English, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Children's Camps, 1954-1960 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Classes-Cosmetics, Sodamen, 1955-1965 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- comite de asuntos hispanos, 1964-1965 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  Spanish
- Community Organization, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Dance, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Dance, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Drug Affairs, 1964-1966 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Education, 1950 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- 1199 Housewarming and FDR Auditorium Dedication, 1957 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Film Forum Programs (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Histradrut and Bonds for Israel, 1955-1963 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Jewish Affair, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Labor Day Parade, 1960-1961 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Latin American Affairs Committee, 1958 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- March to Washington, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Negro Affairs Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Negro History, 1951-1957 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Negro History, 1958-1963 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Pharmacy Colleges, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Purim Party, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Retired Members Program, 1960-1965 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Salute to Freedom, 1964-1966 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Salute to Israel, 1965-1966 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Spanish Classes Special Leadership Classes, 1954-1963 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Special Leadership Classes, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Steward Leadership Classes, 1955-1958 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Theatre, 1965-1967 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Union Versity, 1954-1965 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Women's Auxiliary, 1953-1956 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- A-F, 1950-1956 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- G-L, 1951-1955 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- M-R, 1953-1957 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- S-Z, 1953-1956 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Layoffs, 1964-1966 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Newly Organized, 1959-1970 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Newly Organized, 1959-1970 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Newly Organized, 1959-1970 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Newly Organized, 1959-1970 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Newly Organized, 1959-1970 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Organization-Out-of-Town General, 1964-1966 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Organization-Pennsylvania, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- New and Dropped (all areas) (forms), 1965-1968 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- New and Dropped-Bronx, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- New and Dropped-Brooklyn, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- New and Dropped-Central Manhattan, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- New and Dropped-Lower Manhattan, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- New and Dropped-Nassau Suffolk, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- New and Dropped-Queens, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- New and Delegates, (forms)., 1970-1971 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- New and Delegates, (forms)., 1970-1971 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Dropped Stores, (forms), 1965-1968 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Dropped Stores, (forms), 1965-1968 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Dropped Stores, (forms), 1965-1968 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Dropped Stores, (forms), 1970-1972 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Dropped Stores, (forms), 1970-1972 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Dropped Stores, (forms), 1970-1972 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Lists of Union Drug Stores, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Lists of Union Drug Stores, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Negotiation, 1949 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Negotiation-Associations, 1951 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Negotiation-Independents & Associations, 1953-1955 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Negotiation-Independents & Associations, 1953-1955 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Negotiation, 1954-1956 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Negotiation, 1957-1963 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Negotiation, 1957-1963 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Negotiation, 1957-1963 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Negotiation, 1957-1963 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Negotiation, 1957-1963 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Negotiation, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Negotiation-Associations, 1964-1966 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Negotiation-Luncheon Meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Negotiation-Pharmacists in Hospitals, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Negotiation-Meetings, 1966-1968 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Negotiation-1966-1968 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Negotiation-Committees, 1966-1968 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Negotiation-Committees, 1966-1968 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Negotiation, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Negotiation, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Negotiation, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Negotiations-Bel-Mar Labs, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Negotiation-Brooklyn, 1966-1968 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Negotiation-Brooklyn, 1966-1968 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Negotiation-Crown-Shoprite, 1964-1966 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Negotiation-Empire City, 1966-1968 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Negotiation-Hudson National, 1967-1971 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Negotiation-Kings County Research Labs., 1966 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Negotiation-LaGuardia, 1968-1969 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Negotiation-Liggett, 1966-1968 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Negotiation-Liggett, 1966-1968 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Negotiation-Nassau-Suffolk, 1966-1968 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Negotiation-National Independent Pharmacists, 1966-1968 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Negotiation-NLRB, 1966 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Negotiation-Nescott, 1966-1968 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Negotiation-NY Pharmacists Association, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Negotiation-Non-Associations, 1966-1968 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Negotiation-Queens County, 1966-1968 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Negotiation-Supermarkets, 1966-1968 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Negotiation-Whelan's, 1966-1968 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Bedford-Williamsburg Medical Group, 1969-1970 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Bronx County Pharmaceutical Group, 1941-1964 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Bronx County Pharmaceutical Group, 1941-1964 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Bronx County Pharmaceutical Group, 1941-1964 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Bronx County Pharmaceutical Group, 1941-1964 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Central Bronx Medical Group, 1971-1973 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Circle Manhattan Medical Group, 1968-1972 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Consolidated Brooklyn Retail Pharmacists, Inc., 1947-1963 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Consolidated Brooklyn Retail Pharmacists, Inc., 1947-1963 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Consolidated Brooklyn Retail Pharmacists, Inc., 1947-1963 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Drug Industry Associates, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- East Nassau Medical Group, 1958 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Empire City Pharmaceutical Society, 1966 (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Jamaica Medical Group, 1958-1968 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Kings County Research Labs, 1968-1970 (Box 90, Folder 15)
- Kings County Research Labs, 1968-1970 (Box 90, Folder 16)
- Kings Highway Medical Group, 1958-1970 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Kings Highway Medical Group, 1958-1970 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Kings Highway Medical Group, 1958-1970 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Kings Highway Medical Group, 1958-1970 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Kings Highway Medical Group, 1958-1970 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Morris County Pharmaceutical Society, 1963 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Nassau-Suffolk Pharmacists Association, Inc., 1956-1964 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- National Independent Pharmacists, 1941-1963 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- National Independent Pharmacists, 1941-1963 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- National Independent Pharmacists, 1941-1963 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- National Independent Pharmacists, 1941-1963 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- National Independent Pharmacists, 1941-1963 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- National Independent Pharmacists, 1941-1963 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- New York Pharmacists Association, Inc., 1959-1963 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- New York Retail Druggists' Association, 1951-1963 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- New York State Pharmaceutical Association, 1945-1946 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- North Harlem Pharmaceutical Association, 1951-1955 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- North Harlem Pharmaceutical Association, 1951-1955 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Pharmaceutical Council of Greater NY, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Queens County Pharmaceutical Society, 1955-1964 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Retail Druggist's Association, 1945-1948 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Retail Druggist's Association, 1945-1948 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Washington Heights Medical Group, 1958-1965 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Employer's Association's-General, 1950-1966 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Employer's Association's-General, 1950-1966 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Employer's Association's-General, 1950-1966 (Box 93, Folder 13)
- Employer's Association's-General, 1950-1966 (Box 93, Folder 14)
- Bronx, 1957-1960 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn, 1951-1952 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn, 1951-1952 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn, 1951-1952 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn, 1951-1952 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- East Manhattan, 1950-1962 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Long Island, 1950-1962 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Long Island, 1950-1962 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Lower Manhattan, 1950-1962 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Lower Manhattan, 1950-1962 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Nassau-Suffolk, 1950-1962 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Upper Manhattan, 1950-1962 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Upper Manhattan, 1950-1962 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Upper Manhattan, 1950-1962 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Upper Manhattan, 1950-1962 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- A.J. Medical Supply, Inc., 1965 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- A. W. A. Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Ackerman Pharmacy, 1957-1958 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Actuarial Tabulating Corporation, 1963 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Albert Pharmacy, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Alger Pharmacy, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Almanac Drug, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Alvin Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 96, Folder 8)
- Amazon Drugs, 1962 (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Ambassador Chemists, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 10)
- America Pharmacy, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 11)
- American Women's Club Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 96, Folder 12)
- Apthorp Pharmacy, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 13)
- Arco Pharmacy, 1949-1956 (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Arfre Luncheonette, 1958-1959 (Box 96, Folder 15)
- Argus Drug Store, 1958-1959 (Box 96, Folder 16)
- Art Chemists Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 96, Folder 17)
- Asness Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 96, Folder 18)
- As tor Hotel Pharmacy, 1942-1951 (Box 96, Folder 19)
- Automatic Drug Service, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 96, Folder 20)
- Avenue L Pharmacy, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 21)
- Avignon Pharmacy, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 22)
- B & H Pharmacy, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 23)
- Barbizon Plaza Pharmacy, 1940-1956 (Box 96, Folder 24)
- Barrow Plaza, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 25)
- Barth Drug, Inc., 1954-1960 (Box 96, Folder 26)
- Bauer's Valley Pharmacy, 1962 (Box 96, Folder 27)
- Beekman Tower Hotel, 1950-1956 (Box 96, Folder 28)
- Bell Drug Company, 1940-1950 (Box 96, Folder 29)
- Bellemar Luncheonette, 1954-1955 (Box 96, Folder 30)
- Bendiner & Schlesinger, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 31)
- Biltmore Pharmacy, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 32)
- Bliss Pharmacy, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 33)
- Block Drug Store, 1950-1957 (Box 96, Folder 34)
- Booker Pharmacy, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 35)
- Bowman Pharmacy, 1951-1952 (Box 96, Folder 36)
- Boyd Chemists, 1954-1956 (Box 96, Folder 37)
- Brant Chemists, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 38)
- Breitenbach Pharmacy, 1944-1946 (Box 96, Folder 39)
- Brentwood Pharmacy, 1962 (Box 96, Folder 40)
- Bruckner-Woodbury, 1957 (Box 96, Folder 41)
- Caso, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Caswell-Massey Pharmacy, 1955-1956 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Caswell-Massey Pharmacy, 1955-1956 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Caswell-Massey Pharmacy, 1955-1956 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Caswell-Massey Pharmacy, 1955-1956 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Caswell-Massey Pharmacy, 1955-1956 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Caswell-Massey Pharmacy, 1955-1956 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Caswell-Massey Pharmacy, 1955-1956 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Cambridge Chemists, 1956 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Central Bio-Analytical Labs, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Central Bio-Analytical Labs, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Chadaby's Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Chalanor Pharmacy (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Chalfonte Pharmacy, 1950-1952 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Columbia Medical Company, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Columbian Shoppe, 1953-1955 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Columbian Shoppe, 1953-1955 (Box 98, Folder 9)
- Concord Pharmacy, 1959 (Box 98, Folder 10)
- Consolidated Brooklyn, 1951 (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Continental Pharmacy, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Co-op Pharmacy, 1950-1952 (Box 98, Folder 13)
- Cooper Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 98, Folder 14)
- Courtesy Drug, 1964-1971 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Courtesy Drug, 1964-1971 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Crane Chemists, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Creston Drug Company, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Cromwell Pharmacy, 1950-1954 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Crown Drug, 1951-1954 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Crown Drug, 1951-1954 (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Crown-Shoprite, 1963-1966 (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Crown-Shoprite, 1963-1966 (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Crown-Shoprite, 1963-1966 (Box 99, Folder 10)
- Crown-Shoprite, 1963-1966 (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Cunningham Pharmacy, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Dale Drugs, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Dan Supreme, 1970-1972 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Davidson, 1945-1948 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Davis-Edwards Pharmacol Corp., 1962-1965 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Daytz Pharmacy, 1954 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- DeShaw Drug, 1951 (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Del Carmen Pharmacy, 1951-1955 (Box 100, Folder 7)
- Dichter Pharmacy, 1950 (Box 100, Folder 8)
- Dorwich Chemist, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 9)
- Dwight's Coffee Shop, 1965-1966 (Box 100, Folder 10)
- Eaton Chemists, 1952 (Box 100, Folder 11)
- Economy Drugs, 1951-1952 (Box 100, Folder 12)
- Eden Pharmacy, 1954-1955 (Box 100, Folder 13)
- Edmore Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 100, Folder 14)
- Elm Chemists, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 15)
- Engel Pharmacy, 1944 (Box 100, Folder 16)
- Eton Chemists, 1950-1952 (Box 100, Folder 17)
- Eton Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 100, Folder 18)
- Feldman Pharmacy, 1951-1953 (Box 100, Folder 19)
- Fifteen Twelve Drug Store, 1954 (Box 100, Folder 20)
- Fifth Avenue Chemists, 1946-1951 (Box 100, Folder 21)
- Fifty-Fourth St. Pharmacy, 1956 (Box 100, Folder 22)
- Fifty-Seventh St. Chemists, 1952 (Box 100, Folder 23)
- Fisher, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 24)
- Flower Pharmacy, 1954 (Box 100, Folder 25)
- Frederic Chemists, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 26)
- Freistadt Pharmacy, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 27)
- Friedgen Pharmacy, 1954 (Box 100, Folder 28)
- Fuller Drug, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 29)
- Ganbarg Pharmacy, 1940-1945 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Garcia Pharmacy, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Garfinkle Pharmacy, 1952 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Genovese Drug, 1942-1947 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Genovese Drug, 1964-1968 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Genovese Drug, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- George Washington Chemists, 1955 (Box 101, Folder 7)